Contact

00905446434048 (Mobile) hasanozkul@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/hasan-o-53825a6 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

metaverse

Ethereum

Solidity

Languages

English

Turkish (Native or Bilingual)

Arabic

Certifications

The Complete Solidity Course - Blockchain - Zero to Expert

Near Certified Developer

Hasan O.

Co-Founder and CEO at GptVerse Inc.

Antalya, Turkey

Summary

I have been working as an MSc computer engineer in the software industry for 16 years .I have worked in evm-based blockchains as a blockchain developer for the last 5 years. Throughout my working life, I have worked in corporate companies such as Huawei, Kuwait Turk Bank, Turkcell.

Experience

GptVerse Inc.

Co-Founder

June 2022 - Present (1 year 4 months)

Wilmington, Delaware, Birleşik Devletler

Multi-Platform Ai Hub

Millicent

Senior Blockchain Engineer March 2022 - August 2022 (6 months)

United Kingdom

- -Cosmowasm blockchain fork and Rust Contract Development on it.
- -Big-Dipper Block Explorer Development
- -Bdjuno fork and development for token contract parsing mechanism

Turkcell

Master Expert Blockchain Developer

October 2020 - March 2022 (1 year 6 months)

Maltepe, Istanbul, Turkey

- Self Sovereign Identity Dapp Development with Hyperledger Indy. Turkcell Proov Project
- Interoperator Blacklist Project with Quorum. Blockchain Turkcell GSM Blacklist Project
- Interoperator Fraud Project with Quorum Blockhain . Turkcell GSM Fraud Project
- NFTCell NFT Marketplace Project Development

Kuveyt Turk Participation Bank

Blockchain Engineer

December 2018 - September 2020 (1 year 10 months)

Kocaeli, Turkey

- BIGA Gold-Backed Crypto Project with Quorum Blockchain
- Research and Development of Disruptive Technologies (Blockchain...)
- We work with Agile methodologies
- Azure Devops CI/CD, Kubernetes Hybrid Cloud
- DDD & Microservice Architecture
- C#.Net Core & React & Typescript
- %100 Coverage with Unit Tests

bitmatrixtr

Crypto Exchange Software Manager

August 2018 - December 2018 (5 months)

Istanbul, Turkey

Bitmatrix was crypto exchange company that was subdiary of Aktifbank. I was software development manager at Bitmatrix

IMPAY

Founder

February 2018 - August 2018 (7 months)

Ankara, Turkey

Project Management Activities

Impay Mobile QR Based Blockchain Payment System Development

ATGV

Senior Full Stack Developer

October 2015 - February 2018 (2 years 5 months)

Ankara, Turkey

Jquery,html,Java,Rest Services & IBM Websphere

SDT Space And Defence Technologies

Senior Software Engineer

October 2014 - October 2015 (1 year 1 month)

Ankara, Turkey

Development Of Radar Signal Analysis Applications with Java, C++ SigLib

ATGV

Software Engineer

December 2011 - October 2014 (2 years 11 months)

Page 2 of 3

Ankara, Turkey

Java, Jsp, Html, Jquery, Ajax and Oracle PLSQL

Huawei

R&D Software Developer

February 2010 - May 2011 (1 year 4 months)

Istanbul, Turkey

I worked about

- -Development of DPI software(C++)
- -Development of NGIN services.(Java)
- -Development of fixed IN services.
- -Testing services with CppUnit at Huawei R&D Department in Istanbul.

Karbil Yazılım Software Engineer

October 2008 - August 2009 (11 months)

Istanbul, Turkey

Ziraat Bank TSK Prepaid Wallet Project Development Backoffice Application Development and C# Web Services

Education

Istanbul Technical University

BS, Computer Science Department · (2002 - 2007)

Hacettepe Üniversitesi

Research Doctorate, Computer Science · (2014)

Cankaya University

MS, Master of Computer Engineering (2011 - 2013)

Çankaya Üniversitesi

Master's degree, Computer Engineering · (2011 - 2013)